Hilpert, Elmer E. Arbitration Papers 5493
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bemis Brothers Bag Co. vs. UPP, Local 194, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  6/12/62. Issue: schedules of work - overtime
- Bentzinger Brothers Inc. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  8/10/72. Issue: assignment of overtime
- Biederman Furniture Co. vs. Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, Local 980, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  12/16/60. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Biederman Furniture Co. vs. RCIA, Local 655, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  5/14/69. Issue: discharge - dishonesty
- Biederman Division (American National Stores, Inc.) vs. IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  4/18/73. Issue: contracting out - elimination of jobs
- Biological Research Inc. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  11/14/63. Issue: layoff - discharge
- Black, Sivalls and Bryson, Inc. vs. USA, Local 1962, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  6/28/64. Issue: classification of jobs - evaluation of job factors
- Bliss, E. W., Co. vs. USA, District 27 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Bliss, E. W., Co. vs. USA, District 27, Local 4396. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Booth Fisheries Corp., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, IBT, Local 688, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  12/14/61. Issue: assignment of jobs - rates of pay
- Booth Fisheries Corp., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, IBT, Local 688, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  3/19/64. Issue: Discipline - Discharge
- Borden Co. vs. Int'l Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 2, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  10/25/67. No decision
- Borden, Inc., Columbus Coated Fabrics Co. vs. TWUA, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  7/7/64. No decision
- Borden, Inc., Columbus Coated Fabrics Co. vs. TWUA, Local 487, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  3/9/72. Issues: briefs (no decision) - strikes, slowdowns and work stoppages - wildcat strikes - discharge
- Borden, Inc., Columbus Coated Fabrics Co., vs. TWUA, Local 487, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  7/22/72. Issue: insurance - acceptable plans
- Borden, Inc., Columbus Coated Fabrics Co., vs. TWUA, Local 487, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  4/30/73. Issue: theft
- Borden Co., St. Louis Ice Cream Division vs. IUOE, Local 2, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  12/26/67. Issue: vacancies - assignment of jobs
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  3/11/58. Issue: overtime - assignment of
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  5/12/58. Issue: transfers - management rights
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  10/29/59. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  2/23/61. Issue: assignment of jobs - contracting out
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  6/6/64. Issue: discipline - discharge - insubordination
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  5/4/67. No award
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  6/30/67. Issue: assignment of jobs - contracting out
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  12/5/67. Issue: contracting out
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Products Division vs. AIW, Local 979, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  6/10/68. No award
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  5/20/69. Issue: holiday pay - illness.
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  11/16/69. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  9/4/70. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  3/26/71. Issue: absences -tardiness; discipline - warnings
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  11/6/71. Issue: rates of pay - seniority - call in
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  7/1/72. Issue: assignment of jobs - classification of jobs
- Borg-Warner Corp., Marvel-Schebler Div. vs. AIW, Local 979, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  12/26/73. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Borg-Warner Corp., Norge Div. vs. AIW, Local 370, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  7/12/63. Issue: classification of jobs - transfers between classifications
- Borg-Warner Corp., Norge Div. vs. AIW, Local 370, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  2/22/65. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Boyles Brothers Drilling Co. vs. USA, Local 7034, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  1/10/69. Issue: transfer - termination of operation
- Brand Names, Inc. vs. RCIA, Local 229, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  10/18/68. Issue: vacation pay
- Brinks, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 610, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  2/27/74. Issue: lunch periods - unpaid
- Brockway Glass Co., Inc. vs. GBBA, Local 61, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  1/22/66. Issue: discipline - discharge - illness - failure to report
- Brockway Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 196, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  1/19/68. Issue: promotion - seniority
- Brockway Glass Co. vs. GBBA, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  9/30/69. No award
- Brockway Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 66, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  1/27/70. Issue: rates of pay
- Brockway Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 155, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  2/16/70. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit
- Brown Shoe Co., 17th and Lucas Plant, St. Louis, Missouri vs. United Shoe Workers of America (USW), Local 101-A, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  4/4/55. Issue: vacation pay - layoff.
- Brown Shoe Co., Mattoon, Illinois vs. USW, Local 126A, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  9/22/53. Issue: overtime, discipline - union activities and membership; layoff - seniority
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  6/5/61, 6/8/61, 6/10/61. Issues: rates of pay, rates of pay, layoff
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  6/20/61. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  9/16/61. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  9/18/61. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  9/22/61. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  5/16/63. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Murphysboro, Illinois vs. UMW, District 50, Local 12,652, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  5/11/64, 5/12/64, 5/13/64, 5/13/64. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., St. Louis, Missouri vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  2/22/73. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Brown Shoe Co., Salem, Illinois vs. USW, Local 132-A, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  1/28/54. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., 17th and Lucas Plant, St. Louis, Missouri vs. USW, Local 101-A, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  4/4/55. Issue: vacation pay - layoff
- Brown Shoe Co., Union, Missouri vs. USW, Local 231, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  11/6/53. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Brown Shoe Co., Union, Missouri vs. USW, Local 231, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  11/5/54. Issues: working conditions, rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Union, Missouri vs. USW, Local 231, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  1/26/55. Issue: rates of pay
- Brown Shoe Co., Wohl Shoe Co. Division vs. IBT, Local 688, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  2/18/69. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Brunswick Corp., Sherwood Medical Industries vs. IBT, Local 688, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  9/30/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Brunswick Corp., Sherwood Medical Industries vs. IBT, Local 688, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Buckeye Cotton Oil Co. vs Food, Tobacco and Agricultural Division of Distributive Processing and Office Workers of America, Local 19, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  8/15- 16/51. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Buckeye Cotton Oil Co. vs Food, Tobacco and Agricultural Division of Distributive Processing and Office Workers of America, Local 19, 1951 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  8/17- 18/51. Issue: rates of pay
- Buckeye Cellulose Corp. vs. Buckeye Cellulose Independent Union, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  12/29/69. Issue: rates of pay - overtime
- Bucyrus-Erie Co. vs. USA, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  11/24/69. No decision
- CF and I Steel Corp. vs. USA, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  6/3/69. Settled
- California Spray-Chemical Corp. vs. ICW, Local 462, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  5/9/58. Issue: safety - protective clothing and equipment
- Camden Hydraulics Co., Inc. vs. IAM, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  1/10/67. Withdrawn
- Carbondale, Illinois Seven-Up Bottling Co. vs. IBT, Local 947, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  6/11/53. Issue: reinstatement - following quitting
- Cargo Carriers, Inc. vs. Marine Officers Association, IBT, Local 54, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  3/23/66. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Carlson Products Co., Inc. vs. IUE, Local 825, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  8/20/57. Issue: discipline - supervisors authority
- Carling Brewery Co. vs. IBEW, Local 309, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  3/12/58. Issue: vacation pay - rates of pay
- Carling Brewing Co. vs. Int'l. Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers of America, Local 21, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  5/18/60. Issue: overtime - notice
- Carling Brewing Co. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 21, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  3/1/61. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Carling Brewing Co. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 21, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  6/7/61. Issue: management rights - reduction in force
- Carling Brewing Co. vs. Brewery Workers, Local 21, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  7/28/61. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Carson, Pirie, Scott and Co. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  2/2/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Carps, Inc. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers Union, IBT, Local 688, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  12/27/64. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Carter Carburetor Corp. vs. UAW, Local 819, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  10/13/48. Issue: leaves of absence - union business
- Carter Carburetor Corp. vs. UAW, Local 819, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  10/9/48. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Carthage Marble Corp. vs. OCAW, Local 5-500, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  2/23/67. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. vs. UAW, Local 974, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  7/22/58. Issue: management rights - workweek reduction
- Celotex Corp., Madison, Illinois vs. USA, Local 4971, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  5/10/60. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Celotex Corp., Marrero, Louisiana vs. OCAW, Local 4-179., 1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  5/29/68. Issue: assignment of jobs - seniority
- Central Fibre Products, Co., American Folding Box Division vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union, Local 409, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  12/27/56. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Central Hardware (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Notes - no decision
- Central Hardware Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, Local 688, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  5/29/67. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Central Hardware Co. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  10/22/74. Issue: contracting out - bargaining unit work
- Century Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1108., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  10/8/56. Issue: rates of pay
- Century Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1108., 1958 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  9/17/58. Issue: recall - following strike
- Century Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1108., 1959 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  10/3/59. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Century Electric Co. vs. IUE, Local 1108., 1963 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  5/31/63. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Cerro De Pasco, Lewin Mathes Division vs. USA, Local 4294, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 14-15)
  5/2/58. Issue: management rights - contracting out
- Cerro De Pasco, Lewin Mathes Division vs. USA, Local 4294, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  5/14/62. Issue: assignment of jobs - downgrading
- Certain-Teed Products Corp. vs CLGW, Local 36, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  6/4/63. Issue: rates of pay
- Certain-Teed Products Corp. vs CLGW, Local 36, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  6/25/65. Issue: assignment of jobs - qualification
- Certain-Teed Products Corp., Gustin-Bacon Division vs. IBT, Local 41, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  7/3/70. No decision
- Certain-Teed Products Corp., Gustin-Bacon Division vs. IBT, Local 41, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  12/18/72. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Champion Papers, a division of U.S. Plywood-Champion Papers, Inc. vs. UPP, Local 1967, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  2/22/69. Issue: Assignment of jobs
- Champion Int'l. Corp. vs. IWA, Local 5-355, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  7/14/72. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Champion Int'l. Corp. vs. IWA, Local 5-478, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  6/30/71. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Champion Int'l. Corp., Mengel Cabinet Division vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America (CJA), Local 1199, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  11/21/66. No decision
- Chance, A. B., Co. vs. IUE, Local 821, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  7/1/63. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Chance, A. B., Co. vs. IUE, Local 821, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  5/23/66. Issue: management rights - workweek - rates of pay
- Chattanooga Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 99., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  11/11/69. Issue: promotions - seniority
- Chattanooga Glass Co. vs. GBBA, Local 99., 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  12/24/69. Issue: vacation pay
- Chemcoke, Inc. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 15,196, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  3/25/65. Issue: rates of pay - shift differentials
- Chicago Bridge and Iron Co. vs. USA, Local 7283, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  11/22/68. Issue: classification of jobs
- Chicago Bridge and Iron Co. vs. USA, District 37, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  6/24/69. Settled
- Chris-Craft Corp. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 15,149, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  8/29/66. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Christian Welfare Hospital vs. Service Employees Int'l. Union (SEIU), Local 50, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  6/28/73. Issue: seniority, recall
- Chromcraft Corp. vs. Upholsterers' Int'l. Union (UIU), Local 25, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  7/26/61. Issue: classification of jobs
- Cincinnati Post and Times-Star vs. Stereotypers' Union #5, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  7/11/60. Issue: overtime
- Cities Service Petroleum Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-210, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Clarken Co. vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers' Union, IBT, Local 688, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  10/7/65. Issue: contract interpretation - effective date
- Cleo Wrap Corp. vs. UPP, Local 766, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  6/2/67. Issue: discipline - demotion as
- Clow Corp. - Streator Clay Pipe vs. UBCW, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 21-22)
  3/17-18/67. Issue: rates of pay, classification of jobs
- Clow and Sons, Inc. vs. UBCW, Local 469., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  8/31/67. Issue: rates of pay
- Coca-Cola Bottling Corp. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  6/27/62. Issue: added duties - contract interpretation
- Coca-Cola Bottling Corp. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  12/26/63. Issue: rates of pay - holidays
- Collins Radio Co. vs. IUE, Local 787, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  5/10/63. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work
- Columbus and Southern Ohio Electric Co. vs. IBEW, Local 1466, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  6/27/67. Issue: discipline - suspensions
- Complete Auto Transit, Inc. vs. Office Employees Int'l. Union, Local 13, 1953 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  6/15/53. Issue: rates of pay - increase; vacation eligibility
- Consolidated Aluminum Corp. vs. Aluminum Workers Int'l. Union (AWU), Local 245, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  10/31/74. Issue: assignment of jobs - past practice - transfers
- Consolidated Aluminum Corp vs. AWU, Local 220, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  8/6/68. Issue: strikes - wildcat - discipline
- Container Corp. of America vs. UPP, Local 609., 1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  4/19/68. Issue: rates of pay - overtime
- Container Corp. of America vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 415, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  6/2/62. Issue: rates of pay - classification of jobs
- Container Corp. of America vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union (UPIU), Local 746, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  2/25/74. Issue: reduction in force - work distribution - job classifications
- Container Corp. of America vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union (UPIU), Local 746, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  2/27/75. Issue: discipline - suspension - union activities
- Container Corp. of America vs. United Paperworkers Int'l. Union (UPIU), Local 746, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  2/28/75. Issue: assignment of jobs - multiple machine operation
- Container Stapling Corp. vs Congress of Independent Unions, Local 13, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  11/5/65. Issue: layoff - seniority
- Continental Baking Co. vs. American Bakery and Confectionery Workers Int'l. Union, Local 4, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  8/10/60. Issue: elimination of job
- Continental Can Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, Local 683, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  7/8/66. Settled.
- Continental Grain Co. vs. Int'l. Brotherhood of Longshoremen, Local 1642, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  6/18/57. Issue: working conditions - crew size
- Cooperative Farm Chemicals Association vs. OCAW, Local 5-613, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  3/17/60. Issue: arbitrability
- Cooperative Farm Chemicals Association vs. OCAW, Local 5-613, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  12/17/65. Issue: discipline - suspension
- Copley Press, Inc. - Illinois State Journal and Illinois State Register vs. Springfield Typographical Union, Int'l. Typographical Union of North America (ITU), Local 177, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  4/9/65. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Corhart Refractories Co. vs. IBFO, Local 219, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  1/27/56. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Corhart Refractories Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 14,084, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  5/3/59. Issue: management rights - schedules of work
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  2/10/64. Issue: contracting out - construction work
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-662 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-662, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  5/30/61. Issue: reporting pay - lack of work
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-662, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  4/28/61. Issue: discipline - layoff as
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-662, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  4/30/61. Issue: classification of jobs - discontinuance of classification and/or job
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 7-662, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  5/10/61. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  10/10/70. Issue: rates of pay
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  10/24/58. No decision
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  2/21/59. Issue: classification of jobs - interdepartmental transfer of job
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  2/23/59. Issue: rates of pay
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  2/28/59. Issue: rates of pay
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Corn Products Co. vs. OCAW, Local 5-617, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  3/1/59. Issue: rates of pay
- County Lumber Co. vs. Building Material, Construction, Ice and Coal Drivers, Helpers, Warehousemen and Yardmen, Local 682, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  7/13/64. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Crab Orchard Cooperative Coal Co. vs. UMW, District 12, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  5/14/64. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Cramer Posture Chair Co., Inc. vs. USA, Local 2720, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  3/6/64. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Crown Cork and Seal Co., Plant #12, vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers, Local 688, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  11/9/59. Issue: contract interpretation, rates of pay
- Crown Cork and Seal Co., Plant #12, vs. Warehouse and Distribution Workers, Local 688, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  6/5/62. Issue: rates of pay
- Crunden Martin Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 1540, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  3/2/56. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Cryovac Co. vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America (URW), Local 426., 1956 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  12/8/56. Issue: discipline - discharge.
- Curtis Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 1128., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  10/31/46. Issue: rates of pay
- Curtis Manufacturing Co. vs. USA, Local 1128., 1946 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- Cutler-Hammer, Inc. vs. IAM, Local 664, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  3/11/69. Withdrawn
- Dallas Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 69, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  8/31/69. Issue: transfer - seniority
- Dallas Power and Light Co. vs. IBEW, Local 69, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  5/23/71. Issue: arbitrability - overtime assignments - past practice
- Dana Corp. vs. AIW, Local 903, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  1/6/69. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Darling and Co. vs. UMW, District 50, Local 14,029, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  4/18/57. Issue: assignment of jobs - bargaining unit work
- Darling and Co. vs. IBEW, Local 309 and CJA, Local 169, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  7/1/60. Issue: assignment of jobs - added duties
- Dart Industries vs. TWUA, Local 193, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  8/9/70. Issue: assignment of jobs
- Dart Industries vs. TWUA, Local 193, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  8/23/61. Issue: transfer; rates of pay
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  1/26/55. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  8/25/54. Issue: assignment of jobs - shift scheduling
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  8/19/54. Issue: discipline - discharge/layoff
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  9/3/54. Issue: promotion -seniority
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  10/28/54. Issue: rates of pay - incentive pay
- Dazey Corp. vs. UE, Local 810, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  10/13/54. Issue: fringe benefits - rest periods
- Debron Corp., Mississippi Valley Structural Steel Div. vs. IBT, Local 688, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  11/11/73. Issue: rates of pay - shift work
- Des Moines Steel Co. vs. USA, Local 2071, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  1/25/68. No award
- Diamond Chain Co. vs. USA, Local 1697, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  12/24/64. Issue: seniority - shift scheduling
- Diamond Int'l Corp. vs. UPP, Local 844, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  12/16/68. Issue: discipline - layoff
- Diamond Int'l. Corp. vs. Diamond Gardner Employees Independent Union of Middletown, Ohio, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  10/22/72. Issue: vacancies - seniority
- Diamond Int'l. Corp. vs. UPIU, Local 98, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  7/30/74. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Diamond National Corp. - Diamond Fiber Products vs. UPP, Local 844, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  3/15/69. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Dixie Lou Frocks vs. Int'l. Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  10/14/57. Issue: arbitrability - withdrawn
- Douglas Aircraft Co. vs. UAW, Local 1093, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  10/22/64. Issue: classification of jobs
- Dover Corp. - C. Lee Cook Division vs. IAM, Kentucky Lodge 681, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  6/15/73. Issue: discipline - discharge
- Dow Chemical Co. - Dow Metal Products Co. vs. USA, Local 4804, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  5/14/60. Issue: workweek - beginning
- Dow Chemical Co. - Dow Metal Products Co. vs. USA, Local 4804, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  10/20/60. Issue: rates of pay